Finding Aid for College of Literature, Science and the Arts (University of Michigan) records, 1846-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean’s Files 1916-2008
  - 1997-1999
    - Topical Files 1997-1999
      - Admissions and Admissions Committees
        - Organizational Studies 1998-1999 (Box 393)
        - Outreach-LS&A
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Outreach-University
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - P 1998-1999 (Box 393)
        - Pew Higher Education 1998-1999 (Box 393)
        - Position Requests
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Primary Research Scientists
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Promotions
          - 1998-1999
            - General (Box 393)
            - Personnel (Box 401)
          - 1997-1998
            - General (Box 393)
            - Personnel (Box 401)
        - Provost Cantor
          - 1998-1999, 2 folders (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Provost's Retreat-Future of the Faculty and the University October 26-27, 1998 (Box 393)
        - Public Health, School of 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Public Policy, School of 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - R
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Regents
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Research, Computing and Facilities, Associate Dean for
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Research on Learning and Teaching, Center for (CRLT)
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Research, Vice President for
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Retirements
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - ROTC 1998-1999 (Box 393)
        - S
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Sabbaticals
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Scholarship Committee 1998-1999 (Box 393)
        - Scholarships
          - Dean's Merit
            - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
            - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
          - Miscellaneous 1996-1998 (Box 393)
        - Science Learning Center
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Senate Assembly/SACUA
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Senior Professor Lecture 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Social Research, Institute for
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Student Academic Affairs, Office of
          - 1998-1999 (Box 393)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 393)
        - Student Affairs, Vice President for
          - 1998-1999 (Box 394)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 394)
        - Students-General
          - 1998-1999 (Box 394)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 394)
        - Student Governance
          - 1998-1999 (Box 394)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 394)
        - Student Recruitment 1998-1999, 2 folders; 2 audiocassettes (Box 394)
        - Study Abroad, Office of International Programs
          - 1998-1999 (Box 394)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 394)
        - Summer Programs 1997-1998
          - General (Box 394)
          - Personnel (Box 401)
        - T
          - 1998-1999 (Box 394)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 394)
        - Telluride Association
          - 1998-1999 (Box 394)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 394)
          - 1996-1997 (Box 394)
        - Tenure
          - 1998-1999 (Box 394)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 394)
        - Theme Semesters
          - 1998-1999 (Box 394)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 394)
        - Twenty-First Century Program 1997-1998 (Box 394)
        - U 1998-1999 (Box 394)
        - Undergraduate Education
          - 1998-1999, 2 folders (Box 394)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 394)
        - Undergraduate Initiatives
          - 1998-1999 (Box 394)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 394)
        - Undergraduate Research Opportunity Program (UROP)
          - 1998-1999 (Box 394)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 394)
        - United Way Campaign 1998-1999 (Box 394)
        - Visiting Committee
          - 1998-1999, 2 folders (Box 394)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 394)
        - W
          - 1998-1999 (Box 394)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 394)
        - Washtenaw Community College 1998-1999 (Box 394)
        - XYZ
          - 1998-1999 (Box 394)
          - 1997-1998 (Box 394)
  - 1990/91
    - Departments
      - Anthropology (Box 395)
        [ER RESTRICTED until July 1 2021 ]
      - Asian Languages and Literatures (Box 395)
      - Astronomy (Box 395)
      - Biology
        - General (Box 395)
        - External Review (Box 395)
      - Chemistry, 2 folders (Box 395)
      - Classical Studies (Box 395)
      - Communication
        - General (Box 395)
        - Chair Search (Box 395)
      - Economics (Box 395)
      - English (Box 395)
      - Geological Sciences (Box 395)
      - Germanic Languages and Literatures
        - General (Box 395)
        - Students (Box 401)
          [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2066 ]
      - History
        - General (Box 395)
        - External Review (Box 395)
        - Nicholas Steneck (Box 395)
      - History of Art (Box 395)
      - Honors (Box 401)
      - Mathematics (Box 395)
      - Near Eastern Studies (Box 395)
      - Philosophy
        - General (Box 395)
        - External Review (Box 395)
      - Physics
        - General, 3 folders (Box 396)
        - Materials Research Advisory Committee (Box 396)
        - Visiting Committee 1991 (Box 396)
      - Political Science (Box 396)
      - Psychology, 2 folders (Box 396)
      - Romance Languages (Box 396)
      - Slavic Languages (Box 396)
      - Sociology (Box 396)
      - Statistics
        - General (Box 396)
        - External Review (Box 396)
    - Centers, Institutes, Museums, and Programs 1991-1992
      - Afroamerican and African Studies, Center for (CAAS)
        - General (Box 396)
        - Walter Allen 1988-1991 (Box 396)
        - Ali Mazrui 1988-1991 (Box 396)
        - Teshome Wagaw 1979-1992 (Box 396)
      - American Culture (Box 396)
      - Biological Station (Box 396)
      - Botanical Gardens (Box 396)
      - Chinese Studies (Box 396)
      - Classical Art and Archaeology, Interdepartmental Program in (IPCAA) (Box 396)
      - Comparative Literature
        - General (Box 396)
        - External Review (Box 396)
      - Comprehensive Studies, 3 folders (Box 396)
      - English Language Institute (Box 396)
      - Exhibit Museum (Box 396)
      - Film and Video, Program in (Box 396)
      - Great Books (Box 397)
      - Great Lakes and Aquatic Sciences (Box 397)
      - Herbarium (Box 397)
      - Honors Program (Box 397)
      - Institute for the Humanities (Box 397)
      - International Programs, Office of (Box 397)
      - Japanese Studies (Box 397)
      - Judaic Studies (Box 397)
      - Korean Studies (Box 397)
      - Language Lab (Box 397)
      - Linguistics (Box 397)
      - Medieval and Renaissance Collegium (MARC) (Box 397)
      - Museum of Anthropology (Box 397)
      - Museum of Archaeology (Kelsey Museum) (Box 397)
      - Museum of Paleontology (Box 397)
      - Museum of Zoology (Box 397)
      - Residential College (Box 397)
      - Russian and Eastern European Studies (Box 397)
      - Scandinavian Studies (Box 397)
      - Sikh Studies (Box 397)
      - South and Southeast Asian Studies (Box 397)
      - Studies in Religion
        - General (Box 397)
        - Self Study 1989-1990 (Box 397)
      - Women's Studies (Box 397)
  - 1991/1992
    - Departments
      - Anthropology (Box 398)
        [ER RESTRICTED until July 1 2022 ]
      - Asian Languages and Literatures (Box 398)
      - Astronomy (Box 398)
      - Biology (Box 398)
      - Chemistry
        - General (Box 398)
        - External Review (Box 398)
      - Classical Studies (Box 398)
      - Communication (Box 398)
      - Economics (Box 398)
      - English
        - General (Box 398)
        - Bert Hornback (Box 398)
        - Students (Box 401)
          [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2067 ]
      - Geological Sciences
        - General (Box 398)
        - Samuel Outcault 1989-1992, 2 folders (Box 398)
      - Germanic Languages and Literatures (Box 398)
      - History (Box 398)
      - History of Art (Box 398)
      - Mathematics, 2 folders (Box 398)
      - Near Eastern Studies
        - General (Box 398)
        - External Review (Box 398)
      - Philosophy
        - General (Box 398)
        - David Velleman 1988-1991 (Box 398)
      - Physics
        - General, 2 folders (Box 399)
        - External Review (Box 399)
      - Political Science
        - General, 2 folders (Box 399)
        - Daniela Gobetti (Box 399)
      - Psychology, 2 folders (Box 399)
      - Romance Languages (Box 399)
      - Slavic Languages (Box 399)
      - Sociology, 2 folders (Box 399)
      - Statistics (Box 399)
    - Centers, Institutes, Museums, and Programs 1991-1992
      - Afroamerican and African Studies, Center for (CAAS) (Box 399)
      - American Culture
        - General (Box 399)
        - External Review (Box 399)
      - Applied Physics (Box 399)
      - Armenian Studies (Box 399)
      - Biological Station (Box 399)
      - Botanical Gardens (Box 399)
      - Chinese Studies (Box 399)
      - Classical Art and Archaeology, Interdepartmental Program in (IPCAA)
        - General (Box 399)
        - Students (Box 401)
      - Comparative Literature
        - General (Box 399)
        - Students (Box 401)
      - Comprehensive Studies, 2 folders (Box 399)
      - English Language Institute (Box 399)
      - Exhibit Museum (Box 399)
      - Film and Video (Box 399)
      - Herbarium (Box 399)
      - Honors Program (Box 399)
      - Institute for the Humanities
        - General (Box 399)
        - External Review (Box 399)
      - Inteflex (Box 399)
      - International Programs, Office of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 400)
        - Review, 2 folders (Box 400)
        - Director Search (Box 400)
      - Japanese Studies (Box 400)
      - Judaic Studies (Box 400)
      - Korean Studies (Box 400)
      - Language Resource Center (Box 400)
      - Latin American and Caribbean Studies (Box 400)
      - Linguistics
        - General (Box 400)
        - Bill Croft (Box 400)
      - Middle East and North African Studies (Box 400)
      - Museum of Anthropology (Box 400)
      - Museum of Archaeology (Kelsey Museum) (Box 400)
      - Museum of Paleontology (Box 400)
      - Museum of Zoology (Box 400)
      - Museum Curators (Box 400)
      - Residential College (Box 400)
      - Russian and Eastern European Studies (Box 400)
      - Scandinavian Studies (Box 400)
      - South and Southeast Asian Studies (Box 400)
      - Studies in Religion
        - General (Box 400)
        - David Noel Freedman 1989-1992 (Box 400)
      - Women's Studies (Box 400)
  - 1992-1993
    - Departments
      - Anthropology (Box 402)
        [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2029 ]
      - Asian Languages and Cultures (ALC) (Box 402)
      - Astronomy
        - General (Box 402)
        - External Review (Box 402)
      - Biology (Box 402)
      - Chemistry
        - General (Box 402)
        - 5-year Plan 1982-1992 (Box 402)
      - Classical Studies (Box 402)
      - Communication (Box 402)
      - Economics (Box 402)
      - English
        - General (Box 402)
        - External Review (Box 402)
      - Geological Sciences (Box 402)
      - Germanic Languages and Literatures (Box 402)
      - History (Box 402)
      - History of Art (Box 402)
      - Mathematics
        - General (Box 402)
        - External Review (Box 402)
        - Actuarial Science 1986-1992 (Box 402)
      - Near Eastern Studies (NES) (Box 402)
      - Philosophy (Box 402)
      - Physics
        - Folder 1 of 2 (Box 402)
        - Folder 2 of 2 (Box 403)
      - Political Science (Box 403)
      - Psychology
        - General (Box 403)
        - Clinical Psychology Graduate Program (Box 403)
      - Romance Languages (Box 403)
      - Slavic Languages (Box 403)
      - Sociology (Box 403)
      - Statistics (Box 403)
    - Centers/Institutes/Museums/Programs
      - Afroamerican and African Studies, Center for (CAAS) (Box 403)
      - American Culture (Box 403)
      - Applied Physics (Box 403)
      - Biological Station (Box 403)
      - Botanical Garden (Box 403)
      - Chinese Studies (Box 403)
      - Classical Art and Archaeology (Box 403)
      - Comparative Literature (Box 403)
      - Comprehensive Studies Program (CSP) (Box 403)
      - English Language Institute (ELI) (Box 403)
      - Exhibit Museum
        - General (Box 403)
        - Thomas Moore 1988-1992 (Box 403)
      - Film and Video Studies (Box 403)
      - Great Books Program (Box 403)
      - Great Lakes and Aquatic Sciences, Center for (CGLAS) (Box 403)
      - Herbarium (Box 403)
      - Honors Program (Box 403)
      - Humanities, Institute for the (Box 403)
      - Inteflex (Box 403)
      - International Institute (Box 403)
      - International Programs, Office of (OIP) (Box 403)
      - Japanese Studies (Box 404)
      - Judaic Studies (Box 404)
      - Korean Studies (Box 404)
      - Language Resource Center (LRC) (Box 404)
      - Latin American and Caribbean Studies Program (Box 404)
      - Linguistics (Box 404)
      - Medieval and Renaissance Collegium (MARC) (Box 404)
      - Middle Eastern and North African Studies (Box 404)
      - Museum of Anthropology (Box 404)
      - Museum of Paleontology (Box 404)
      - Museum of Zoology (Box 404)
      - Religion, Program on Studies in (Box 404)
      - Residential College (RC) (Box 404)
      - Russian and East European Studies (CREES) (Box 404)
      - Scandinavian Studies (Box 404)
      - Sikh Studies (Box 404)
      - South and Southeast Asian Studies (Box 404)
      - Women's Studies (Box 404)
  - 1993-1994
    - Departments
      - Anthropology (Box 404)
      - Asian Languages and Cultures (ALC) (Box 404)
      - Astronomy (Box 404)
      - Biology (Box 404)
      - Chemistry (Box 404)
      - Classical Studies (Box 404)
      - Communication
        - General (Box 404)
        - Malamuth, Neil (Chair) (Box 474)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2024 ]
      - Economics (Box 404)
      - English (Box 404)
      - Geological Sciences (Box 404)
      - Germanic Languages and Literatures (Box 404)
      - History (Box 404)
      - History of Art (Box 404)
      - Mathematics (Box 405)
      - Near Eastern Studies (NES) (Box 405)
      - Philosophy (Box 405)
      - Physics (Box 405)
      - Political Science
        - General (Box 405)
        - External Review (Box 405)
      - Psychology (Box 405)
      - Slavic Languages (Box 405)
      - Sociology (Box 405)
      - Statistics (Box 405)
    - Centers/Institutes/Museums/Programs
      - Afroamerican and African Studies, Center for (CAAS) (Box 405)
      - American Culture (Box 405)
      - Armenian Studies (Box 405)
      - Biological Station (Box 405)
      - Botanical Gardens (Matthaei) (Box 405)
      - Chinese Studies (Box 405)
      - Classical Art and Archaeology (Box 405)
      - Comparative Literature (Box 405)
      - Comprehensive Studies Program (CSP) (Box 405)
      - English Language Institute (ELI) (Box 405)
      - Exhibit Museum (Box 405)
      - Film and Video Studies
        - General (Box 405)
        - External Review (Box 405)
      - Great Lakes and Aquatic Sciences, Center for (CGLAS) (Box 405)
      - Herbarium (Box 405)
      - Honors Program
        - General (Box 405)
        - Internal Review (Box 405)
      - Humanities, Institute for the (Box 406)
      - Inteflex
        - General (Box 406)
        - Internal Review (LSA component) (Box 406)
      - International Institute, 2 folders (Box 406)
      - International Programs, Office of (OIP) (Box 406)
      - Japanese Studies (Box 406)
      - Judaic Studies (Box 406)
      - Korean Studies (Box 406)
      - Language Resource Center (LRC) (Box 406)
      - Latin American and Caribbean Studies (Box 406)
      - Linguistics (Box 406)
      - Middle Eastern and North African Studies (Box 406)
      - Museum of Anthropology (Box 406)
      - Museum of Archaeology (Box 406)
      - Museum of Paleontology (Box 406)
      - Museum of Zoology (Box 406)
      - Religion, Program on Studies in (Box 406)
      - Residential College (RC) (Box 406)
      - Russian and East European Studies (CREES) (Box 406)
      - Sikh Studies (Box 406)
      - South and Southeast Asian Studies (Box 406)
      - Women's Studies (Box 406)
  - 1994-1995
    - Departments
      - Anthropology (Box 406)
      - Asian Languages and Cultures (ALC) (Box 406)
      - Astronomy (Box 406)
      - Biology (Box 406)
      - Chemistry, 2 folders (Box 406)
      - Classical Studies (Box 406)
      - Communication
        - General (Box 406)
        - Faculty Advisory Committee (Box 407)
        - Journalism Response to Faculty Advisory Committee Charge (Box 407)
        - News Articles (1994-95 Investigation and Reorganization) (Box 407)
      - Economics
        - General, 2 folders (Box 407)
        - External Review (Box 407)
      - Germanic Languages and Literatures (Box 407)
      - History (Box 407)
      - History of Art (Box 407)
      - Mathematics
        - General, 2 folders (Box 407)
        - Calculus (Box 407)
      - Near Eastern Studies (NES) (Box 407)
      - Philosophy (Box 407)
      - Physics (Box 407)
      - Political Science
        - General (Box 407)
        - Meizlish/Brown Censorship Issue (Box 407)
      - Psychology (Box 408)
      - Romance Languages
        - General (Box 408)
        - External Review (Box 408)
      - Slavic Languages
        - General (Box 408)
        - External Review (Box 408)
      - Sociology, 2 folders (Box 408)
      - Statistics (Box 408)
    - Centers/Institutes/Museums/Programs
      - Afroamerican and African Studies, Center for (CAAS) (Box 408)
      - American Culture (Box 408)
      - Applied Physics (Box 408)
      - Armenian Studies (Box 408)
      - Biological Station (Box 408)
      - Botanical Garden (Box 408)
      - British Studies (Box 408)
      - Chinese Studies (Box 408)
      - Classical Art and Archaeology (Box 408)
      - Comparative Literature (Box 408)
      - Comparative Studies Program (CSP) (Box 408)
      - English Language Institute (ELI) (Box 408)
      - Exhibit Museum (Box 408)
      - Film and Video Studies (Box 408)
      - Great Lakes and Aquatic Sciences, Center for (CGLAS) (Box 408)
      - Herbarium (Box 408)
      - Honors Program (Box 408)
      - Humanities, Institute for the (Box 408)
      - Inteflex (Box 408)
      - International Institute, 2 folders (Box 408)
      - Japanese Studies (Box 408)
      - Judaic Studies (Box 408)
      - Korean Studies (Box 408)
      - Language Resource Center (LRC) (Box 408)
      - Latin American and Caribbean Studies (Box 409)
      - Linguistics
        - General (Box 409)
        - Self Study (Box 409)
      - Medieval and Renaissance Collegium (MARC) (Box 409)
      - Middle Eastern and North African Studies (Box 409)
      - Museum of Anthropology (Box 409)
      - Museum of Archaeology (Box 409)
      - Museum of Paleontology (Box 409)
      - Museum of Zoology (Box 409)
      - Museums: Systematic Report (Box 409)
      - Religion, Program on Studies in (Box 409)
      - Residential College (RC) (Box 409)
      - Russian and East European Studies (CREES) (Box 409)
      - Sikh Studies (Box 409)
      - South and Southeast Asian Studies (Box 409)
      - Women's Studies (Box 409)
  - 1995-1996
    - Departments
      - Anthropology (Box 409)
      - Asian Languages and Cultures (ALC) (Box 409)
      - Astronomy
        - General (Box 409)
        - Magellan Project: Memos of Understanding (Box 409)
      - Biology, 2 folders (Box 409)
      - Chemistry, 2 folders (Box 409)
      - Classical Studies
        - General (Box 409)
        - External Review (Box 410)
      - Communication (Box 410)
      - Economics (Box 410)
      - English, 2 folders (Box 410)
      - Geological Sciences
        - General (Box 410)
        - External Review (Box 410)
      - Germanic Languages and Literatures
        - General (Box 410)
        - External Review, 2 folders (Box 410)
      - History (Box 410)
      - History of Art (Box 410)
      - Mathematics
        - General, 2 folders (Box 410)
        - Initiative in Applied and Interdisciplinary External Advisory Committee (Box 410)
      - Near Eastern Studies (NES) (Box 410)
      - Philosophy (Box 410)
      - Physics (Box 411)
      - Political Science (Box 411)
      - Psychology (Box 411)
      - Romance Languages (Box 411)
      - Slavic Languages (Box 411)
      - Sociology, 2 folders (Box 411)
      - Statistics (Box 411)
    - Centers/Institutes/Museums/Programs
      - Afroamerican and African Studies, Center for (CAAS) (Box 411)
      - American Culture (Box 411)
      - Applied Physics (Box 411)
      - Armenian Studies (Box 411)
      - Biological Station (Box 411)
      - Botanical Gardens (Matthaei) (Box 411)
      - British Studies (Box 411)
      - China Data Center (Box 411)
      - Chinese Studies (Box 411)
      - Classical Art and Archaeology (Box 411)
      - Comparative Literature (Box 411)
      - Comprehensive Studies Program (CSP) (Box 411)
      - English Language Institute (ELI) (Box 411)
      - Exhibit Museum (Box 411)
      - Film and Video Studies (Box 411)
      - Great Lakes and Aquatic Sciences, Center for (CGLAS) (Box 411)
      - Herbarium (Box 411)
      - Honors Program (Box 411)
      - Humanities, Institute for the (Box 411)
      - Inteflex (Box 411)
      - International Institute, 2 folders (Box 411)
      - International Programs, Office of (OIP) (Box 411)
      - Japanese Studies (Box 411)
      - Judaic Studies (Box 411)
      - Korean Studies (Box 411)
      - Language Resource Center (LRC) (Box 411)
      - Latin American and Caribbean Studies (Box 411)
      - Linguistics (Box 412)
      - Medieval and Renaissance Collegium (MARC) (Box 412)
      - Middle Eastern and North African Studies (Box 412)
      - Museum of Anthropology (Box 412)
      - Museum of Archaeology (Box 412)
      - Museum of Paleontology (Box 412)
      - Museum of Zoology (Box 412)
      - Religion, Program on Studies in (Box 412)
      - Residential College (RC) (Box 412)
      - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (CREES) (Box 412)
      - South and Southeast Asian Studies (Box 412)
      - Women's Studies (Box 412)
  - 1996-1997
    - Departments
      - Anthropology (Box 412)
      - Asian Language and Cultures (Box 412)
      - Astronomy
        - General (Box 412)
        - Kitt Peak Telescope: Sale, 2 folders (Box 412)
      - Biology (Box 412)
      - Chemistry (Box 412)
      - Classical Studies (Box 412)
      - Communication (Box 412)
      - Economics (Box 412)
      - English (Box 412)
      - Geological Sciences (Box 412)
      - Germanic Languages and Literatures (Box 412)
      - History (Box 412)
      - History of Art (Box 413)
      - Mathematics, 2 folders (Box 413)
      - Near Eastern Studies (NES) (Box 413)
      - Philosophy (Box 413)
      - Physics (Box 413)
      - Political Science (Box 413)
      - Psychology
        - General (Box 413)
        - Clinical Psychology Site Visit (Box 413)
      - Romance Languages
        - General (Box 413)
        - Romance Language Instruction External Review (Box 413)
      - Slavic Languages (Box 413)
      - Sociology
        - General (Box 413)
        - External Review (Box 413)
      - Statistics (Box 413)
    - Centers/Institutes/Museums/Programs
      - Afroamerican and African Studies, Center for (CAAS) (Box 413)
      - American Culture (Box 413)
      - Applied Physics (Box 413)